CURRICULUM VITAE OGBONNA CHIDIEBERE CHINONSO UNIVERSITY COLLEGE HOSPITAL STAFF SCHOOLS, UNIVERSITY OF IBADAN, IBADAN

CARRIER OBJECTIVE: To Contribute Positively to Academic Excellence through Research and Hardwork; as Well as ensure the attainment of the Institutions' Goals and Objectives

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a committed researcher and a PhD student in Chemistry Department, University of Ibadan. I have a broad based theoretical and practical knowledge in chemistry with specialization in Analytical chemistry. I am proficient in computer aided teaching, with good interpersonal and communication skills as well as the ability to work collaboratively and complete assignments before deadlines. My current research interests are Quality control and standardization of herbal medicine, physicochemical properties/Analysis of herbal medicine (i.e. quantitative estimation of bioactive group of compounds like alkaloids, flavonoids, polyphenolic compounds and so on) as well as toxicological studies of herbal medicines.

FULL NAME: OGBONNA, Chidiebere Chinonso

DATE OF BIRTH: 30th March, 1986

GENDER: Male MARITAL STATUS: Single

E-mail Address: Chidexagain@yahoo.com

Mobile Phone Number: 08061551129

Permanent Home Address: EMMANUEL'S ANG. CHURCH, ALOR-UNO, NSUKKA, ENUGU

STATE, NIGERIA

LOCAL GOVERNMENT AREA: NSUKKA

STATE OF ORIGIN: Enugu
NATIONALITY: Nigeria

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS OBTAINED WITH DATES

INSTITUTIONS ATTENDED WITH DATES:

INSTITUTIONS	QUALIFICATIONS	DATE
 UNIVERSITY 0F IBADAN, IBADAN 	M.SC. ANALYTICAL CHEMISTRY	2011– 2013
 UNIVERSITY OF NIGERIA, NSUKKA 	B.Sc. PURE & INDUSTRIAL CHEMISTRY	2005 – 2010
 NATIONAL YOUTH SERVICE CORPS [NYSC] 	NYSC DISCHARGE CERTIFICATE	2010 – 2011
 SAINT TERESA'S COLLEGE, NSUKKA 	WAEC/NECO	1996 – 2001
 URBAN I PRIMARY SCHOOL, NSUKKA 	FSLC	1990 – 1996

WORK EXPERIENCE WITH DATES:

Computer Teacher, Hugtech Information Link, Onuiyi Link Road, Nsukka, Enugu State, [2003 – 2005].

- Industrial attachment at Nigerian Bottling Company, Ninth Mile, Enugu, Enugu State [Quality Control Unit] (2007 2008).
- Chemistry Teacher, Government Senior Secondary School, Zaura-Babba, Ungogo LGA, Kano State (2010-2011).
- Assistant Examiner, West African Examinations Council [2011 till Date].
- Assistant Examiner, National Examination Council (NECO) [2013 till Date]
- Chemistry Teacher, Resurrection Youth Education Center, Chapel of the Resurrection, University of Ibadan, Ibadan. [2013 2014]
- Chemistry Teacher, Afadebo Secondary School, Samonda, Ibadan [2014 2015]
- Chemistry Teacher, Hill Crest High School, Bodija, Ibadan. [2015 2017]
- Part-time Chemistry Teacher, Deeper Life High School, Lagos/Ibadan Express way, Ibadan. [2017]
- Chemistry Teacher, University College Hospital Staff Schools, University of Ibadan [2017 2018]

PUBLICATIONS/PRESENTATION

- Kinetics of solvent uptake by High Density Polyethylene Film: A case study of Aromatic Hydrocarbon Solvent (Unpublished Paper)
- Synthesis and Characterization of Geopolymer Concrete Using Agricultural Waste: A Potential Large Scale Replacement for Concrete Produced From Portland Cement (Unpublished Paper)
- Evaluation of options in Agricultural Waste management: Alkali Production from Cocoa Pod Waste (Unpublished Paper)

SERVICE TO THE NATION: NATIONAL YOUTH SERVICE CORPS [NYSC] – KANO STATE, (2010 – 2011)

COMPETENCIES:

COMPUTER SKILLS – Proficiencies In Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Powerpoint, Corel Draw, Repair And Installations.

EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES: Research, Listening to Music and Watching Football

REFEREE	S:	(Mrs.)
•	Dr.	Mary
	Gilbert	Ogundi
	Adie	ran
		Chemi
	Chemis	stry
	try	Depart
	Depart	ment,
	ment,	Univer
	Univer	sity of
	sity of	Ibadan
	Ibadan,	,
	Ibadan,	Ibadan
	Nigeria	,
	•	Nigeri
	E-Mail:	a.
	<u>Gildie1</u>	E-
	<u>975@g</u>	mail:
	<u>mail.co</u>	mbogu
	<u>m</u>	ndiran
	Phone	@yaho
No:		o.com
08059	998665	Phone
		No:
-	Dr.	08023
	(Mrs.)	30986
	Helen	1
	Alimo	
	h	
	Alabi	
	Chemis	
	try	
	Depart	
	ment,	
	Univer	
	sity of	
	Ibadan,	
	Ibadan,	
	Nigeria	
	E-Mail:	
	helenal	
	abie3@	
	yahoo.	
	com	
	Phone	
	1 110110	

■ Dr.

No: 080283 06868